Do you know me?
l am an entertainer and a connoisseur
We will excel in the third year also
Velu, this is our area
Are you caught?
What did you say?
Is it your area?
This area, that area, that place
or this place, l fear nothing
Because..l am GHILLLl in all areas
You just look back
Are you threatening because
it's your area? l am Otteri Nari
- Hey, Nari, leave him
- No, we should not
Show your might in tomorrow's
Kabaddi match, we'll see.. .go
You might faint
Get lost, come
lf you dare
you will be butchered
You gave him a good snub
-Buddy, you are hot!
-l am Mirchi of Trichy -Come, you cheeky
Go and join an apt frequency
Watch out
Come
l am being hit, save me Velu
Oh God!
Hey, fool, look here
lt is hurting, leave me
Simran sister, save me from being hit
l am a spinster
and do you call me Simran?
Get lost!
Oh God!
Careful Velu
Buddy, he is hanging
- Careful Velu
- Have l not made you dangle in mid air?
That's why, l asked you
not to challenge me
Don't spree
Else, you will be contained
Now it is your turn to go down
Make way for our leader
He is the southern tiger
-Are you down now?
-lt looks like Gemini Circus
Up's and down's are common
But ultimate victoy only counts
Don't leave him
Buddy!!
-Bring it here, put the ladder
-Cops are coming
Both will be caught
What will you do now?
You can play kabaddi, cricket,
do Bharathnatyam..
..or even Kathakili
but should not be arrogant
lf you are, you will topple, now watch.. .
Cops have come
ls it tonsured at Tirupathi?
-Who are you?
-Aathivasi -Do you mean tribal?
l belong to Madras,
so eveyone calls me like this
Eveyone's life has thousands of stages
This is a season of moon
We should escape soon
Hey, come here
turn this side
-What is this wound?
-Puli scratched me
-What? -My friend Pulikesi
touched me and it started bleeding
Uncle, are fingernails poisonous?
Near Anaconda, Titanic,
Jurassic Park and Panagal Park ..
..there is a wine shop
go there, bad boys
Can't you understand?
He's asking you to go home & get boozed
-Get lost.. -Rascal
-He got caught
-Sir, leave my shirt, girls are watching
-Are you a Casanova?
Now-a-days guys like me
only are Casanovas
- Sir, take off your hand
- You look like a damaged tanker lory..
..and you are
bothered about your reputation
- Where is your leader?
- l'll say only if you leave my shirt
- What did you ask?
- Where is your leader?
-Don't talk about him
-What? -Do you know what he did?
-What did he do?
-He turned like this and ran off.. ..
Bangles iingle..
..in the hands
My dear came to my thoughts
on a dampish night
Oh God!
Do you have sense?
You are coming this way
Will you not
come through the front door?
l am a Superman
This is how l will come
You rice sack, why are you
dancing here with these creatures?
Bhuvana, ask him to stop,
else l will bite him?
Listen, don't insult us
They are my friends
Who.. .these quarter and half tickets?
- Go out
- Why...why should l go out?
l too have equal right in this room
Dad said so
She is not even 3 feet tall
but talks about rights
Now, you will go out
-Sachin Tendulkar has come
to the ne_ street -Sachin!!
l wanted to get an autograph
but couldn't find a good shirt
Move aside, eveything is
scattered and damn this doll
-Brother, is it really Sachin?
-Yes, Sachin has come..
..Aishwaya Rai has come with him.. .
-They are shooting an ad film
in the ne_ street -Both of them?
They disappeared like a lightning
-Where is he?
- Who?
After fighting in streets like a rogue
are you playing 'good boy'?
- Sister, mummy.. - This is not
a Police station, but our house
Since morning 6 'O' clock
he is studying sincerely and you are..
ln the entire world, he is only guy
who studies wearing a petticoat
l mistook petticoat for dhoti
- In my exuberance to study...
- Is it so?
Dad, he's lying, don't believe him
Just few minutes back, he came from top
- Why are you covered with soot?
- He only did that
He said Sachin and Aishwaya Rai
has come for shooting
and made us roam in the streets
l didn't say that
l said 'Sachidhananda Swamigal
has come to the nearby temple..
..and you will get
Aishwayam from his blessings'